it's me Angela today I'm going to be
我是安吉拉,今天我将要成为安吉拉
making a flavor for all of the Mario
今天是我 安吉拉 今天我要为马里奥做口味
为所有马里奥人制造一种口味
making a flavor for all of the Mario
characters let's go okay starting off
给马里奥所有人物做调味品 让我们开始吧
人物,我们走吧,好 开始开始
characters let's go okay starting off
with Mario Rainbow Road ice cream donut
人物,让我们去好 开始与马里奥 彩虹路冰淇淋甜甜甜圈
与马里奥·彩虹路冰淇淋甜甜甜圈
with Mario Rainbow Road ice cream donut
on top and hot press
与Mario Rainbow Road 冰淇淋甜甜甜圈在顶端和热媒体上
上键和热按键
on top and hot press
slice vanilla drizzle drizzle God
上顶和上顶的热压切片 香草细雨滴神啊
香草细细雨
slice vanilla drizzle drizzle God
sprinkles
上帝喷洒
喷洒
sprinkles
lastly I have a fondant Mario on top
最后,我有一个可爱的马里奥在上面
this one ended up turning out amazing
最后,我有一个可爱的马里奥 在上面的这一个 最终结果变得惊人
这场比赛的结局是 令人惊叹
this one ended up turning out amazing
next up for Bowser Fireball ice cream
下一个是鲍瑟 火球冰淇淋
接下来是鲍泽火球冰淇淋
next up for Bowser Fireball ice cream
donut on top and hot fries
接下来是鲍塞尔 火球 雪糕甜甜甜甜圈上 上面和热炸薯条上
上面的甜甜圈和热炸薯条
donut on top and hot fries
slice green vanilla drizzle drizzle God
上面的甜甜圈和热炸薯条片 绿色香草树细雨
绿色香草细雨
slice green vanilla drizzle drizzle God
sprinkles yo what's this
绿色香草细细雨滴滴,上帝喷洒你,这是什么?
喷洒你什么 这是什么
sprinkles yo what's this
I got Fireballs I say I have Bowser
我这有火球,我说有鲍泽
我有火球 我说我有鲍瑟
I got Fireballs I say I have Bowser
spikes on top
我有火球,我说上面有弓箭钉
顶部的钉钉
spikes on top
yo this flavor ended up being one big
口味最后变成一个大块头
这口味最后变成一个大
yo this flavor ended up being one big
star okay next up for peach peaches and
这口味最后成了大明星 下一个是桃桃桃
下一个是桃桃桃和桃子
star okay next up for peach peaches and
cream ice cream donut on top and a half
下一个桃桃桃和奶油冰淇淋甜甜甜圈
上面一个半上面的奶油冰淇淋甜甜甜圈
cream ice cream donut on top and a half
price
上半价的奶油冰淇淋甜甜甜圈
价价价
price
sliced pink cream drizzle drizzle God
粉红色奶油冰淇淋滴滴
粉红色奶油细细雨
sliced pink cream drizzle drizzle God
sprinkles
上帝喷洒的粉红色奶油细细雨细雨
喷洒
sprinkles
crowns
喷洒皇冠
皇冠数
crowns
and lastly I have a little toad Army on
皇冠和最后我有一个小青蛙军
最后我还有一支小青蛙军
and lastly I have a little toad Army on
top
最后,我有一个小 青蛙军在上面
顶上
top
what does this one do but ended up
上方的这只究竟做了什么, 结果却成了
这家伙做了什么,但最后却成了
what does this one do but ended up
turning out amazing Bowser would love
鲍瑟会喜欢的
伟大的鲍瑟会喜欢的
turning out amazing Bowser would love
this flavor for sure
神奇的鲍瑟一定会喜欢这种口味的
本字幕由AI大模型生成